[
  {
    "question": "你好吗？",
    "answer": "How are you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "我很好",
    "answer": "I’m good"
  },
  {
    "question": "你叫什么名字？",
    "answer": "What’s your name?"
  },
  {
    "question": "我叫___",
    "answer": "My name is ___"
  },
  {
    "question": "你来自哪里？",
    "answer": "Where are you from?"
  },
  {
    "question": "我来自美国",
    "answer": "I’m from the U.S."
  },
  {
    "question": "多少钱？",
    "answer": "How much is it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "厕所在哪里？",
    "answer": "Where is the bathroom?"
  },
  {
    "question": "可以帮我吗？",
    "answer": "Can you help me?"
  },
  {
    "question": "我想要这个",
    "answer": "I want this one"
  }
]
